I can't believe you'd actually say that.
我真不敢相信你会这么说
I'd much rather be Mr. Peanut than Mr. Salty.
我是盐先生而非花生先生?
No way. Mr. Salty is a sailor.
才怪,盐先生是个水手
He's gotta be the toughest snack there is.
他应该是最顽强的点心
I don't know. You don't wanna mess with Cornnuts.
我不知道,你不会想和玉米作对的
They're crazy.
它们简直是疯了
Oh,my God. You gotta come see this.
上帝呀.你应该看看这个
There's some creep out there with a telescope.
有个变态拿着望远镜
I can't believe it. He's looking right at us.
我真不敢相信他在看我们
Oh,that is so sick.
真呕心
I feel violated.
我感觉被冒犯了
And not in a good way.
而且很不爽
How can people do that?
怎会有人这样?
You guys,look. Ugly Naked Guy got gravity boots.
你们看,丑陋裸男有双重力鞋
The One With the Evil Orthodontist
六人行 第1季 第20集 风流牙医
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
Years from now, school children will study it...
几年后学童将会把它奉为…
...as one of the greatest first dates ever.
第一次约会的经典加以研读
-Yeah. -I'll say,yeah.
-是的 -要我说,当然
It was unbelievable.
它太令人无法置信
We could be ourselves. We didn't have to play games.
我们可以完全作自己,无须再玩任何游戏
-Have you called her? -She'd know I like her. That's crazy.
-你打过电话给她没? -让她知道我喜欢她?你疯了不成
Guys. It's gross.
伙计.你可真毛糙啊
It's the next day. How needy do I wanna seem?
才第二天,你要我显得多渴望?
-I'm right. Right? -Yeah,let her dangle.
-对吧 -对,让她慢慢等吧
I can't believe my parents are pushing me to find one of you people.
我无法相信我爸妈,强迫我找你们这种男人
Come on. Just do it.
快,只管去做
Call her. Stop being so testosterone-y.
拿起电话打给她 别摆出一付臭男人的样子(义同睾丸素)
Which,by the way, is the real San Francisco treat.
对了,旧金山真有这道菜
-Her machine. -Answering machine?
-是机器 -她的答录机?
No,interestingly, her leaf blower picked up.
不,真有意思,是落叶清扫机
So,why didn't you say anything?
你为何不说话?
No. Last time I left a spontaneous message...
不行,上次我留话时
... I ended up using the phrase, "Yes,indeed-io."
结果说了“对,的确”
Look,it's Rachel and Barry. Don't everybody look.
看,是瑞秋和巴瑞,不,别一起看
What's going on?
怎么了?
-They're just talking. -Does he look upset?
-他们只是在讲话 -他是否神情落寞?
Does he look like he was told to shove anything?
他是否像被告知去死的样子?
No. Actually,he's smiling.
没有,而且他正在微笑
Oh,my God. Don't do that.
我的老天,不要那样干?
What? What? What?
怎么啦?怎么啦?怎么啦?
That man across the street just kicked that pigeon.
对街的男人踢了一只鸽子
And basically,that's how a bill becomes a law.
这就是法案成为法律的原因
See? Hey,Rach.
看?嗨,瑞秋
How'd it go?
情况如何?
You know,it was actually really great.
你们知道吗,真的,真的好极了
Lunch at the Russian Tea Room.
他带我到俄国茶室吃饭
I had that chicken,where you poke it and butter squirts out.
我点了那种鸡肉 一刺就有奶油啧出来的那种
Not a good day for birds.
今天真不是鸟儿的好日子
Then we went to Bendel's.
然后我们去精品店
And I told him not to,but he got me a bottle of Chanel.
我告诉他不要,他还是买了香奈儿给我
That's nice. Now was that before or after you told him...
真体贴.是在你跟他说之前还是之后送的
...to stop calling,stop sending flowers and to leave you alone?
叫他别再打电话来, 别再送你花,别再来烦你?
Right. Well,we never actually got to that.
老实说我没机会开口
It was just so nice to see him again.
能再见到他的感觉真好
It was comfortable and it was familiar.
感觉是那么自在而熟悉
It was just nice.
感觉真好
That's nice twice.
你已讲了两遍
Isn't this the same Barry who you left at the altar?
他不是在圣坛前被你甩掉的巴瑞吗?
Where have you been?
你上哪儿去了?
It was different with him today.
今天和他在一起感觉不同
He wasn't,like,Orthodontist Guy.
他今天不像是牙医
I mean,we had fun. Is there anything wrong with that?
我们玩得很开心,这样有什么不对吗?
-Why? -I have my reasons.
-为什么? -我有我的理由
He's engaged to another woman...
他订婚的对象…
...who happens to be your ex-best friend?
是你前任的知己呢?
All right. I know it's stupid.
好吧!我知道这样做很傻
I'll see him this afternoon and put an end to it.
我下午去找他谈分手
I'm not crazy,right? I mean,it was never like that.
我不疯狂吧?我从未像这样
No,it wasn't.
从未
It was so nice having this little sink here.
这儿有个小水槽真好
Then with authority,hang up.
还挂着…证书
Will you just leave her the message?
你到底留言不?
Okay. All right,fine.
好的,这就说
"Oh,Danielle, I wasn't expecting the machine.
丹妮尔,没想到是答录机接的
Give me a call when you get a chance.
有空请回电
Bye-bye.
再见
Oh,God.
哦,天哪
That's what you've been working on for two hours?
你这两小时都在忙这个?
Hey,I've been honing.
我在演练
-What was with the dishes? -She might think I'm in a restaurant.
-和盘子有何关系? -我要她以为我在餐厅
I might have a life. Like I haven't been sitting here...
我过着不错的生活
... honing for the last two hours?
不是只在这儿演练数小时的样子
-The telescope guy's doing it again. -Oh,my God.
-看,又是那个拿望远镜的人. -哦,我的上帝
Go away. Stop looking in here.
拜托,走开,别再往这儿看
Great. Now he's waving back.
这下可好,他也挥手了
We gotta do something.
我们得想办法阻止他
I caught him looking into our place. I feel like I can't do stuff.
早上我逮到他往这儿看 真是令我毛骨惊然,我感觉自己无法办事
What kind of stuff?
什么样的事情呀?
Will you grow up? I'm not talking about sexy stuff...
成熟点行吗,我不是指性
...but,like, when I'm cooking naked.
我只是光着屁股做饭
You cook naked?
你光着屁股做饭?
Yeah,toast,oatmeal. Nothing that spatters.
对,吐司,燕麦,不会溅出来的东西
What are you looking at me for? I didn't know that.
看我干嘛?我毫不知情
What's the matter?
怎么了?
I just Oh,Barry,this was not good.
巴瑞,这样不好
No,it was. It was very,very good.
不,不好.是非常非常不好
-What about Mindy? -Way better than Mindy.
-明蒂呢? -我们干得比明蒂好多了
I mean,what about you and Mindy?
不,我是指你和明蒂
If you want,I'll break it off with her.
如果你愿意我就和她分手
No,don't do that. Not for me.
万万不行,别那样做.别为我那样做
Dr. Farber,Bobby Rush is here for his adjustment.
法大夫,巴比来做调整
Thanks,Bernice.
谢谢
Let's go away this weekend.
我们周末去渡假
-This is all way too -No,we can go to Aruba.
-巴瑞,这样太… -不,或许我们可以去阿鲁已
When I went there on what would've been our honeymoon...
我在“蜜月”时去过了
...it was really nice. You would've liked it.
感觉很棒,你一定会喜欢的
I had a bra.
我本来有穿胸罩
Hey,Dr. Farber.
法大夫
All right,Miss Greene, everything looks fine.
格林小姐,看来一切正常
We're starting to see some real progress.
进步许多
-What? -I'm 1 2,I'm not stupid.
-干嘛? -我十二岁了,我不笨
Can I use your phone?
能借用你的电话吗?
For future reference, that thing in your hand...
我指点你一下,你拿的那支…
...can also be used as a phone.
…也可以当电话使
Yes,it's working.
这电话没问题啊
-Why isn't she calling? -Maybe she never got your message.
-她为何不回电? -或许她没听到你的留言
Call her machine, and if she has a lot of beeps...
如果愿意你可以打给她的留言机 如果她听见许多哔声
...that means she didn't get her messages yet.
那代表她或许没听见留言
-Doesn't that make me seem? -Desperate? Needy? Pathetic?
-难道你不认为这样会使我感觉有点 -绝望,渴望,可悲?
You obviously saw my personal ad.
你显然看过我的霉友启事
How many beeps?
哔几声?
She answered.
她接的
This is where you'd use that "hello" word.
此时你该向她打招呼才对
I won't talk to her. She got my message...
我不能跟她讲话,她显然听到我的留言
...and is choosing not to call me. Now I'm needy and snubbed.
而且选择不回电,我既渴望又被人冷落
God,I miss just being needy.
我真想念纯渴望的滋味
So how'd he take it?
嘿,他表现如何?
Pretty well,actually.
事实上,还不错
How come you have dental floss in your hair?
你头发上为何有牙线?
Oh,do l?
有吗?
-We ended up having sex in his chair. -You had sex in his chair?
-我们在他椅上做爱 -你们在他椅上做爱?
I said that a little too loudly,didn't l?
我是否说得太大声?
You had what?
你们什么?
Sex in his chair.
在他椅上做爱
What...? What were you thinking?
你到底在想什么?
I don't know. We still care about each other.
我也不知道,我们仍在乎对方
There's a history there. It's like you and Carol.
我们曾相爱过,就像你和卡萝一样
It's nothing like me and Carol.
不,不像我和卡萝
If she said to you, "Ross,I want you on this couch...
如果她说:罗斯我要你躺在这沙发上
... right here,right now," what would you say?
此时此地,你会怎么回答?
If it helps,I could slide over.
如果需要我可以过去点
It's a totally different situation. It's apples and oranges.
这完全是两回事,这是苹果和桔子
It's orthodontists and lesbians I gotta go.
牙医和女同志,我走了
-Where are you going? -I just have to go.
-你要上哪儿去? -我就是要走,行吗?
I have things to do with my life.
我有自己的人生要过
I have a jam-packed schedule.
我有许多事要做
And I am late for keeping up with it,okay?
被某事耽搁了
Mindy.
明蒂
How are you?
你好
Yes,I heard. Congratulations. That is so great.
对,我听说了,恭喜.这真是太好了
Really,oh,God
真的,哦,上帝啊
I'm working tomorrow,but if you want,you can come by if you'd like.
我明天要上班,如果愿意可以到店里
Great.
太好了
So I'll see you tomorrow.
明天见了
Okay. Bye.
ok,再见
Oh,God. Oh,God.
天呀 天呀 天呀
So how's Mindy?
明蒂好吗?
She wants to see me tomorrow. She sounded weird. I gotta call Barry.
她明天想见我, 她的语调好诡异,我得打电话给巴瑞
It's me. I just Mindy.
是我,我只是,明蒂
Mindy. No,I figured that's where you'd be.
明蒂.我想你可能会在那儿
Hell is filled with people like you.
你这种人都该下地狱
He's back. The peeper's back.
偷窥狂又出现了,蹲下
-Get down. -Get down?
-蹲下? -蹲下?
And boogie.
接着跳舞
I gotta go and get my eyes scratched out by Mindy.
我得去上班,接受明蒂的审判
She may not even know.
放轻松,或许她还不知道
I haven't heard from her in seven months,what else is it about?
拜托,我们七个月来没连络过 她突然打电话来还会有什么事呢?
She was my best friend.
她曾是我最要好的朋友
We went to camp together, she taught me how to kiss....
我们一起去夏令营,她教我如何亲吻
Now,you know, I'm,like,the other woman.
是吗?如今我像是成了第三者
-I feel so -Naughty.
-我感觉自己很…-顽皮
-See you later. -I'll walk with you.
-回头见了.-我和你一起出去
When she taught you to kiss,were you wearing any kind of little uniform?
她在夏令营时教你亲吻,你穿着制服,或着…
That's fine,yeah.
没事了.
I'm going to the bathroom. Will you watch my phone?
我要上洗手间,帮我守着电话好吗?
-Take it with you. -We haven't had a second date...
-你何不带进去? -我们还没第二次约会
-...she needs to hear me pee? -Why don't you call her?
-她需要听到我尿尿的声音吗? -何不干脆打给她?
I can't. I left a message. I have some pride.
我已留言,不能打给她.我有男性的尊严
-Do you? -No.
-有吗? -没有
Danielle,hi.
丹妮尔
It's Chandler.
是我,钱德
I'm fine.
我很好
Listen....
听着…
I don't know if you tried to call me because...
我不知道你是否打过电话给我
... I accidentally shut off my phone.
因为我是个白痴不小心把电话关了
That's fine. That's great. Okay.
好,太好了
She's on the other line. She's gonna call me back.
她正在讲电话,等一下会回我电话
She's on the other line, she's gonna call me back.
她正在讲电话,等一下会回我电话…
-Don't you have to pee? -That's why I'm dancing.
-你不想尿了? -这就是我跳舞的原因
-Mindy. -Hey,you.
-明蒂. -嗨,你好
Hey,you.
嗨,你好
So what's up?
什么事?
We should really be sitting for this.
我们该坐下来谈
Sure we should.
当然啦
I'm gonna ask once, and I want a straight answer.
我只问一次,我希望你直接回答
Not like when I asked if those red pants made my ass look big.
这好像在问,红色短裤是不是 让我的屁股显得大一些一样
I know things have been weird...
我感觉最近有点奇怪
...but you're my oldest friend, except for Laurie...
你是我认识最久的朋友,除了萝瑞之外
...who's bitter because she lost weight...
她虽已减肥成功
...and it turns out, she doesn't have a pretty face.
但是,脸蛋依然丑陋
-Okay,I'm just gonna say it. -Okay.
-我要说了啊. -好的
Will you be my maid of honor?
愿意当我的伴娘吗?
-Of course. -That's so great.
-当然! -太好了
It is. It is. It is.
这是,这是,这是
-That's all you wanted to ask? -That's all.
-这就是你想问我的事? -对,就这样
-What? -That's not all.
-怎么了? -不,不只这样
-Oh,sure it is. -Oh,no,it isn't.
-当然是的 -也不全是
I think Barry's seeing someone in the city.
我认为巴瑞有其他的女人
What would make you think that?
你怎会这样想?
Since the engagement, he's acted weird.
宣布订婚后他就变了样
And then last night,he came home smelling like Chanel.
昨晚他回家时有香奈儿的味道
Really?
真的?
If it'll make you feel any better...
如果这样能让你好过点
...when Barry and I got engaged, he was weird too.
我和巴瑞订婚时他也变了样
Oh,God. That's what I was afraid of.
瞧,这就是我最担心的
What's what you were afraid of?
什么?你担心什么?
When Barry was engaged to you, he and l...
巴瑞和你订婚时,我跟他…
... kind of had a little thing on the side.
…正在偷偷恋爱
-What? -I know,I know.
-什么? -我知道
When he proposed,people said,"He'll do to you what he did to Rachel."
他向我求婚时,每个人都劝我别接受 他会待你像瑞秋一样
And now I feel so stupid.
如今我只觉得自己好笨
You are so stupid.
明蒂,你真笨
We are both so stupid.
我们两人都笨
What do you mean?
什么意思?
Smell familiar?
是不是熟悉的味?
Oh,I'm so sorry.
抱歉…
Oh,no,me. I am so sorry.
不,是我抱歉…
No,I am sorry. I'm sorry.
不,我对不起,我抱歉
Oh,my.
哦,我的上帝
Four letters,"circle or hoop."
四个字母,圈圈或圆圈
-Ring,damn it,ring. -Thanks.
-快响呀,该死的,快响呀. -谢啦
-You know our phone's not working? -What?
-我们的电话坏了. -什么?
I called and there was no answer.
我从咖啡店打给你没有回电
I turned it off.
我关机了
Mother of God,I turned it off.
天啊,我关机了
Just like you told her you did.
和你告诉她的一样
Just pointing out the irony.
真是讽刺
I went across the street to the doorman.
我和对街门房谈过了
I got the peeper's name. Can I use the phone?
他告诉我那偷窥狂的名字,电话能借用吗?
Can I use your phone?
电话能借用吗?
The number for a Sidney Marks,please.
请帮我查辛尼马克斯的电话
"Heating device."
热装置?
Radiator.
散热器
Five letters.
五个字母
"Rdtor."
“Rdtor.”
Yeah,is Sidney there?
是辛尼吗?
Oh,this is? Sidney's a woman.
辛尼是个女的
So she's a woman,so what?
是女的又怎样?对,那又怎样?
Yeah,so what?
对,那又怎样?
I live across the street,and I know about your telescope.
我住在对街.我注意到你拿着望远镜
And I don't appreciate it.
而且我很不喜欢你这样
Yeah,I can see you right now. Hello?
我现在就看的见你,hello
If I wanna walk around in my underwear,I shouldn't have to feel
如果我要穿着内裤在室内走,我无须感觉…
Thank you.
谢谢
That's not really the point. The point is,that
那不是重点,重点是…
Mostly free-weights, but occasionally
大部份是高速公路,偶尔
Yeah,my neighbor. Yeah,the brunette.
对,我邻居,对,黑褐色头发
She said you looked pretty that day in the green dress.
她说你穿绿色套装很好看
The green dress? Really?
绿色套装?真的?
She said you looked like lngrid Bergman.
对,她说你像英格丽褒曼
Did she mention me?
他提到我了吗?
She wants to know why you tie the towel around your head.
她想知道为什么你头上顶块毛巾
It's a leave-in conditioner,okay?
那是调节器,行不行?
It's a leave-in conditioner.
那是调节器
-You got a second? -Sure,sure.
-你有时间吗? -当然,当然
Come on...
进来啊…
-...in. -Hello,sweetheart.
hello,亲爱的
What you guys doing here?
你们来干什么?
We are here to break up with you.
我们是来和你分手的
Both of you?
你们两个?
We think you're a horrible person, and bad things should happen to you.
基本上我们认为你是个大烂人 你该遭到天打雷劈
I'm sorry. God,I am so sorry.
对不起…我是个白痴
I was weak. I couldn't help myself.
我是个懦夫,我无法自拔
Whatever I did,I only did because I love you so much.
不管我做什么都是因为太爱你了
Which one of us are you talking to there?
巴瑞,你是指哪一个?
Mindy.
明蒂
Of course,Mindy. It was always Mindy.
当然是指明蒂.我一直深爱着明蒂
When we were having sex in that chair?
即使我们在你椅上做爱?
I swear,whatever I was doing, I was thinking of you.
我发誓,不论我做什么我都想着你
Please. That second time,you couldn't have picked her out of a lineup.
拜托,第二回合时你连她姓啥都忘了
You did it twice?
你们做了两次?
The first time didn't really count. You know,it was Barry.
第一次不算,你了解巴瑞的
Honey,sweetheart,look. Just give me another chance.
明蒂,我亲爱的,再给我一次机会
We'll start over. We'll go back to Aruba.
我们再重新来过,我们再到阿鲁巴去
What is it with you and Aruba? Do you have a deal with the airlines?
你和阿鲁巴有什么关系? 你和航空公司有协议吗?
What do you say?
你怎么说?
Dr. Farber,we've got an emergency here.
法大夫,紧急状况
Jason Castalano 's choking on his retainer.
强森被自己的牙套噎到了
Oh,God. I'll be right there,Bernice.
拜托,我马上去
Look,please don't go anywhere.
请别离开
I'll be right back.
我马上回来
Okay,and we'll be here, hating you.
我们会在这儿的,在这儿恨你
See how he was sweating when he walked out?
看见他走出去时满身大汗没?
If I'm hogging the ball, you jump right in there...
这样吧,我去抓住他那里,然后你跳过去
...and take some punches. This feels great.
…狠狠打他几拳.那感觉一定很爽
I'm pretty sure I'm still gonna marry him.
是吗?我还是想嫁给她
What are you talking about?
你在说什么?
Mindy,the guy is the devil.
明蒂,那家伙是个恶魔
He is Satan in a smock.
是个衣冠禽兽
I know he's not perfect.
我知道他并不完美
But the truth is at the end of the day,I still really wanna be...
老实说我还是想当
... Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber...
巴瑞牙医的…
... D. D.S.
…太太
Oh,God.
我的天
I hope you can find a way to be happy for me.
希望你能为我高兴
And I hope you'll still be my maid of honor.
我希望你还愿意当我的伴娘
And I hope Barry doesn't kill you and eat you in Aruba.
我希望巴瑞在阿鲁巴不会将你宰了然后吃掉
You okay?
你还好吗?
Really?
真的吗?
Since I ran out on Barry at the wedding...
自从我在婚礼上抛下巴瑞
...I've wondered whether I made the right choice.
我一直在想这决定是否正确
And now I know.
如今我已得到答案
I'm so glad.
我真为你高兴
Big day.
大日子
I'll give you this: Mr. Peanut is a better dresser.
告诉你花生先生的穿着比较讲究
He's got the monocle, he's got the top hat....
他有单片眼镜,高帽
Did you know he's gay?
你知道他是个男同志吗?
I just wanna clarify this. Are you outing Mr. Peanut?
我只想知道你判花生先生出局?
Danielle,hi.
丹妮尔
Everybody,this is Danielle. Danielle,everybody.
各位,她叫丹妮尔, 丹妮尔,这是大家
Why are you here?
你为何会出现在这儿?
I've been calling, but I had your number wrong.
我一直打电话给你都一直打错号码
When I got the right one, there was no answer.
最后问查号台知道你的号码 却没人接电话
So I thought I'd come down here and make sure you were okay.
我想来看看你是否无恙
I'm okay.
我没事
Maybe we could get together later?
或许我们改天可以见个面
That sounds good. I'll call you. Or you call me,whatever.
这主意不错,我再打给你 或是你打给我
You got it.
一言为定
-Bye,everybody. -Bye.
-再见了,各位. -再见
-There you go. -Second date.
-你会和她. -二次约会
I don't know.
我不知道
You don't know?
你不知道?
She seems nice,but her coming all the way here...
她好像很不错,她大老远来这儿
...just to see if I was okay? I mean,how needy is that?
只想确定我没事,有这必要吗?